Guide to the University Archives photograph collection, 1861-ongoing UA.01.15.0009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Activities Series, 44 Boxes, approx. 22,000 items
  - Preparing Minorities for Academic Careers [Apprentices and General] (Box 70)
  - Preparing Minorities for Academic Careers [General] (Box 70)
  - Pre-School Nursery - East, 1969, 1952, 1960 (Box 70)
  - Pre-School and Primary Program, 1970 (Box 70)
  - Primate Center (Box 70)
  - Project Pride, 1978-1979 (Box 70)
  - Psychology Department (Box 70)
  - Public Safety (Box 70)
  - Quadrangle Pictures (Box 70)
  - Quadrangle Pictures [Promotional Pictures] (Box 70)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1938 [10th Birthday Party] (Box 70)
  - Radio - Campus Time Show (Box 70)
  - Red Friars (Men's Honorary) (Box 70)
  - Registration (Box 71)
  - Relics (Box 71)
  - Religion, Department of (Box 71)
  - Religious Council (Box 71)
  - Religious Life (Box 71)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps., 3 folders (Box 71)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps. - Air Force (Box 71)
  - Resident Advisor Training Slides, 1998 (Box 71)
  - Retiree Association, Duke University, 1983 [Officers] (Box 71)
  - Rhodes Scholars (Box 71)
  - Romances Languages Department (Box 71)
  - Sailing Club (Box 71)
  - Sandals (Women's College Honorary Service) (Box 71)
  - Scholarships - A.B. Duke Scholars Reception, 1970 (Box 71)
  - Scholarships - T.W. Minah Scholarship Fund (Box 71)
  - Science Clubs, 1923 (Box 71)
  - Science - Math Conference (Box 71)
  - Science Writers Conference, 1970 (Box 72)
  - Science Writers Check Presentation, 1970 (Box 72)
  - Sea Level Hospital (Box 72)
  - Seminars [The South in Continuity and Change; Humanities and the Arts] (Box 72)
  - Sewage School (Waterworks School) (Box 72)
  - Ship - S.S. William P. Few (Box 72)
  - Sigma Chi - Fraternities (Box 72)
  - Sigma Gamma, 1926 (Box 72)
  - Sigma Pi Sigma (Physics Honorary) (Box 72)
  - Slavic Languages, Department of (Box 72)
  - Social Responsibility Conference, 1977 (Box 72)
  - Sociology, Department of (Box 72)
  - Songs, Duke University (Box 72)
  - Sororities (Box 72)
  - Sororities, Black (Box 72)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly - Editors (Box 72)
  - Southern Governor's Regional Growth Board, 1971 (Box 72)
  - Spanish Institute, 1940s (Box 72)
  - Spanish Institute, 1950s and n.d. (Box 72)
  - Spastic Dormitory (Box 72)
  - Speech Therapy, 1968 (Box 72)
  - Sports Information (Box 72)
  - Springfest (Box 72)
  - Student Army Training Corps (SATC) (Box 72)
  - Student Project for University Development (SPUD) (Box 72)
  - String Quartet (Box 72)
  - Student Hangouts - Durham [See also Student Life 1960s] (Box 72)
  - Student Life (Box 72)
  - Student Life [Campus] (Box 72)
  - Student Life [Student Interviews (Time Magazine)] (Box 72)
  - Student Life [Student Forum (outside), n.d.] (Box 72)
  - Student Life [Trinity College, c. 1892-1910] (Box 72)
  - Student Life [Trinity College, C. 1910-1924] (Box 72)
  - Student Life [1920s] (Box 72)
  - Student Life, 1930s (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1938-1940 (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1940s [Exterior Scenes] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1940s [Interior Scenes #1] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1940s [Interior Scenes #2] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1940-1944 [Interior Scenes] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1940-1944 [Exterior Scenes] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1946, 1947 [From Chanticleer] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1950s [Exterior Scenes] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1950s [Interior Scenes] (Box 73)
  - Student Life, 1950s (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1953, 1955 [Class of 1955] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1956 (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1960s [Exterior Scenes] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1960s [Interior Scenes] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1960s [Students on Campus] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1966 [Students on Campus] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1966 [Fog - Street on Campus] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1966 [East Campus Development Brochure] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1967 [Campus/Students] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, c. 1967 [Student Studying] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1968 [Student Seminar Outdoors] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1968 ["Girls in the Garden"] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1968 [Students on Campus (view from the Chapel)] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1967 [Students in Library ] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1967 [Seminar Students] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1968 [Duke Gardens, Girl Studying and Dog] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1969 [Students Living Off-Campus] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1969 [Study Abroad Students] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1969 [Campus Pictures for Brochure] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1969 [Student Feature for Alumni Register] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1970s [Interior Scenes] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1970s [Exterior Scenes #1] (Box 74)
  - Student Life, 1970s [Exterior Scenes #2] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1980s, 2 folders (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1984-1985 [Class of 1986] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1990s (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 2000s (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1970s [Exterior - Concerts, Festivals, Etc.] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1970 [Campus] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1971 [Campus] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1971 (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1972 ["Carologue" Authors] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1971 [East Campus], 2 folders (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1973 [Chemistry Students and Classes] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1976 [Spirit of 1976 Duke Power Bus] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1970s [Students in Frat House Lounge] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1970s [Student Making Pots] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1970s [Residence Hall Brochures] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, 1970 [Angier Duke Students] (Box 75)
  - Student Life, late 1970s (Box 75)
  - Student Life [Classroom Scenes] (Box 75)
  - Summer School Opening, 1970 (Box 75)
  - Summer Session (Box 75)
  - Summer Theater at Duke (Box 75)
  - Symposium, 1966 (Box 76)
  - Symposium Speakers, 1983 [Christopher Lasch, Robert Coles, Stuart Ewen] (Box 76)
  - Symposia - Miscellaneous (Box 76)
  - Taurian Players (Box 76)
  - Tax Institute (Box 76)
  - Tombs Initiation, 1924 (Box 127)
  - Testing and Guidance, Bureau of (Box 76)
  - Theatre: Long Day's Journey into Night, 1986 (Box 76)
  - Tobacco Advertisements [See also Durham, W. Duke & Sons Factories] (Box 76)
  - Tobacco Advertisements [W. Duke & Sons Albums] (Box 76)
  - Tombs, c. 1916 (Box 76)
  - Train, the Duke University (Box 76)
  - Tree Lighting (Box 76)
  - Triangle Universities Nuclear Laboratory (TUNL) (Box 76)
  - Triangle Universities Nuclear Laboratory (TUNL), 1968 [Nuclear Acc. And Cyclotron] (Box 76)
  - Trinity College (Box 76)
  - Trinity Park School Club (Box 76)
  - Trinity College Development Advisory Committee (Box 76)
  - Trustees, Trinity College, 1924 (Box 76)
  - Trustees, Trinity College (Box 76)
  - Trustees, Duke University and Duke Endowment, 1956 [See also Founder's Day 1956] (Box 76)
  - Trustees, Duke University (Box 76)
  - Trustees (Endowment) Tour Library (Box 76)
  - University Archives (Box 76)
  - University Center (Box 76)
  - University Planning Committee (Box 76)
  - University Staff, General (Box 76)
  - University Development, Leadership Conference (Box 76)
  - University Staff, Employee Awards (Box 76)
  - University Stores (Box 76)
  - University Union (Box 77)
  - UNC - Duke Relations (Box 77)
  - Victory Bell [See also Cheerleaders] (Box 77)
  - Vigil [See: Demonstrations] (Box 77)
  - Visitors (Box 77)
  - Vocarillon Recital, 1939 (Box 77)
  - WDBS and WXDU (Box 77)
  - White Duchy (Box 77)
  - Wiley Gray Medal (Box 77)
  - Wind Symphony (Box 77)
  - Wind Symphony, 1969 [Rehearsal] (Box 77)
  - Woman's Dramatic Club - Trinity College, 1922 ["Monsieur Beaucaire"] (Box 77)
  - Women's College Development Advisory Committee (Box 77)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellows (Box 77)
  - Women's Student Government Association (Box 77)
  - World War II at Duke [Armed Services #1] (Box 77)
  - World War II at Duke [Armed Services #2] (Box 77)
  - World War II at Duke [Student Activities, etc.] (Box 77)
  - YMCA (Box 77)
  - YMCA Convention, 1906-1907 (Box 77)
  - Young Republican Club (Box 77)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (Box 77)
  - Zoology Department (Box 77)
- Buildings Series, 23 Boxes, approx. 11,500 items
  - Durham [Aerial Views] (Box 78)
  - Durham, 1960 [Duke Homesites, Pinecrest Road] (Box 78)
  - Durham [(Former Married Student Housing)] (Box 78)
  - Durham [Watts Hospital] (Box 78)
  - Durham [Trinity Park Neighborhood Area] (Box 78)
  - Durham [Duke Homestead] (Box 78)
  - Durham, 1940 [Duke Homestead] (Box 78)
  - Durham [Four Acres (University House)] (Box 78)
  - Durham [Duke Tobacco Factories] (Box 78)
  - Durham [General, Including Lincoln Hospital] (Box 78)
  - Durham, 1973 [Walltown Charitable Community Center] (Box 78)
  - Trinity College, Randolph County (Box 79)
    - General Views (Box 79)
    - Homes (Box 79)
    - Randolph County Folder List (Box 79)
    - Athletics, Baseball, 1891 (Box 79)
    - Athletics, Football, 1888-1892 (Box 79)
    - Athletics, Tennis Court (Box 79)
    - Bell (Box 79)
    - Main Building (Box 79)
    - Gazebo, 1984 [Dedication] (Box 79)
    - Main Building with Students in Front, 1891 (Box 79)
    - Classes, 1872 [Class of 1872] (Box 79)
    - Classes [Class of 1874] (Box 79)
    - Classes [Class of 1875] (Box 79)
    - Classes [Class of 1876] (Box 79)
    - Classes, 1878 [Class of 1880] (Box 79)
    - Classes [Class of 1887] (Box 79)
    - Classes [Class of 1891] (Box 79)
    - Classes [Class of 1892] (Box 79)
    - Faculty, 1878-1879 [Faculty Groups] (Box 79)
    - Faculty [Individual Photos] (Box 79)
    - Student Life, 1890 [Womanless Wedding] (Box 79)
    - Phi Delta Theta, 1878, 1879 (Box 79)
    - Students [Group Photos] (Box 79)
    - Students [Portraits] (Box 80)
  - Theological Society (Ministerial Students), 1891 (Box 80)
  - Union Institute (Randolph County) [(Conjecture)] (Box 80)
  - Brown's Schoolhouse (Randolph County) [(Conjecture)] (Box 80)
  - Trinity Guard, 1861 (Box 80)
  - Trinity Park School [Faculty] (Box 80)
  - Trinity Park School [Students] (Box 80)
  - Admissions (2138 Campus Drive) [(President's House)] (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views, c. 1931 [East and West Campuses] (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views [East Campus] (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views [East Campus (color)] (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views [Trinity College (Durham, NC)] (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views, c. 1927-1953 [West Campus], 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views, c. 1954-1973 [West Campus] (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views [West Campus (color)] (Box 80)
  - Aerial Views [Allen Building] (Box 80)
  - Alspaugh Hall [Trinity College Dormitory] (Box 81)
  - Alumni Memorial Gymnasium (East Campus) (Box 81)
  - Aquatic Center (West Campus) (Box 81)
  - Anne Roney Fountain (East Campus) (Box 81)
  - Architectural Details [Contact Prints and Negatives], 2 folders (Box 81)
  - Architectural Models, Masonry (Box 81)
  - Architectural Models, Frank Clyde Brown Scrapbook, 1924 (Box 81)
  - Architectural Drawings, H. Trumbauer [Negatives] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Ackland Art Museum (Proposed)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Aerial View and Plot Plan (East Campus)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Aerial View and Plot Plan (West Campus)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Allen Building] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Baldwin Auditorium] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Chapel - Interior] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Dining Hall (West Campus) - Interior] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Dormitory Groups and Union (West Campus)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Few Quadrangle, Tower] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Hospital] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Chapel - Exterior] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer, to 1947 [Library, Perkins] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Main Court (West Campus)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Main Entrance, Duke University] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Medical School] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Physics Building] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [School of Forestry, Proposed Building] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Religious Education Building - Exterior and Interior Chapel] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Union Cloisters (West Campus)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Union (West Campus)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Wallace Wade Stadium] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, H. Trumbauer [Duke's Chapel United Methodist Church] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, 1960 [Library (West)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches (Central Campus) (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches (Trinity College) (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches (West Campus) (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches, Trumbauer [Indoor Stadium (Cameron)] (Box 81)
  - Architectural Sketches [East Campus (Renderings)] (Box 82)
  - Architectural Sketches [Biddle Music Building] (Box 82)
  - Architecture - British / Duke Associations (Box 82)
  - Ark - Angier Duke Gymnasium (Box 82)
  - Art Building (East Campus) (Box 82)
  - Art Department [(Darkroom)] (Box 82)
  - Art Museum (Box 82)
  - Art Museum [Renovation] (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1968 [Brummer Collection] (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1969 (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1969 (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1968 [For Alumni Register] (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1971 [African Art Exhibit] (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1970 [Old Ladies Quilting] (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1971 [Nude Exhibits] (Box 82)
  - Art Museum, 1972 [Docents Program] (Box 82)
  - Asbury Building (East Campus) (Box 82)
  - Athletic Fields (Trinity College) (Box 82)
  - East Residence Hall (formerly Aycock Hall) (Box 82)
  - Baldwin Auditorium (Box 82)
  - Basset Hall (Box 82)
  - Bells (East Campus) (Box 82)
  - Benches (Box 82)
  - Biological Sciences Building (Box 82)
  - Bishop's House (East Campus) (Box 82)
  - Bivins Building (Box 82)
  - Botany (Box 82)
  - Branson Theater (Box 83)
  - Brown Dormitory (East Campus) (Box 83)
  - Bryan Center, 1982 [Dedication] (Box 83)
  - Bryan Center (Box 83)
  - Bryan Center [Groundbreaking and Construction] (Box 83)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium [Exterior] (Box 83)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium [Construction] (Box 83)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium [Interior] (Box 83)
  - Campus Drive (Box 83)
  - Campus East and West [Color Negatives] (Box 83)
  - Campus Views, 1928-1931 [East Campus] (Box 83)
  - Campus Views, c. 1940 [Stock Images] (Box 83)
  - Campus Views [News Service Stock Images] (Box 83)
  - Campus Views [Earl Gilbert, Photographer] (Box 83)
  - Campus Views, to 1938 [West Campus, Charles K. Knell] (Box 83)
  - Campus Views [Robert D. Little] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [West, Wootten-Moulton] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1932-1938 [Academic Quad, Richardson] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1932-1938 [Chapel, Carillon, Richardson] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1932-1938 [Hospital, Richardson] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1932-1938 [Residential Quads, Richardson] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1932-1938 [General] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1932-1938 [East, Richardson] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [Duplicates] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [East Campus] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [East Campus, Construction] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [Snow Scenes] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [Panoramas] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1890s [Trinity College (Durham, NC)] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views, 1910/1911-1924 [Trinity College (Durham, NC)] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [Trinity College - Snapshots] (Box 84)
  - Campus Views [West] (Box 85)
  - [West, Residential Quads] (Box 85)
  - Card Gymnasium [West Campus] (Box 85)
  - Carillon (Box 85)
  - Carillon, Construction (Box 85)
  - Carr Building (Box 85)
  - Central Campus Apartments (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Artist's Representations] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Duplicates for Exhibits] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Dacus Plaque] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Aerial Views] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Cross-Campus Views] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Detail] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Events & Crowds] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Midrange Frontal Views] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior at Night] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Side / Rear Views] (Box 85)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Snow scenes, Fog] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Viewed from Academic/Residential Quads] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Exterior, Color] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Interior] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Construction, Prevatt / Stewman Photos] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Construction ] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Construction, Photocopies] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Construction, J.A. Stewman Collection] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Construction, Snapshots], 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Construction, J.A. Stewman Collection], 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Stonemasons] (Box 86)
  - Chapel [Cornerstone] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Crypt] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Interior, General Views] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Interior, Memorial Chapel] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Interior, Charles E. Knell] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Interior, Nave] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Organ, Aeolian] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Organs] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Organs, Flentrop] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Organs, Flentrop] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Repairs] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Services, Crowds, Weddings] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Services (Brochures)] (Box 87)
  - Chapel, 1938 [Sunrise Easter Service] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Windows] (Box 87)
  - Chapel [Windows (Sutherland) and Scaffold] (Box 87)
  - Chapel Drive Buildings (Box 87)
  - Old Chemistry Building (Box 87)
  - Christmas Tree (Box 87)
  - Commonwealth House (Box 87)
  - Computer Lab, AROD Building, West Campus Computer Center Fire, 1969, 1980 (Box 87)
  - Jack Coombs Field (Box 87)
  - Construction and Landscaping, 1960s (Box 88)
  - Construction (East Campus) (Box 88)
  - Construction and Landscaping [Progress Pictures (Copy Prints)] (Box 88)
  - Construction and Landscaping [West Campus, Snapshots] (Box 88)
  - Construction and Landscaping [West Campus, General Views] (Box 88)
  - Craven Memorial Hall [See also MC 10] (Box 88)
  - Cornerstone Laying, Union Building, 1928, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Cornerstone Laying, Union Building, 1928 [Ceremony] (Box 88)
  - Craven Quadrangle (Box 88)
  - Crowell Quadrangle and Tower (Box 88)
  - Crowell Science Building (Box 88)
  - Crowell Science Building [Interior] (Box 88)
  - Crowell Science Building, 1890s [Interior] (Box 88)
  - Decorations on Buildings, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Decorations on Buildings [Statues, etc.] (Box 89)
  - Decorations on Buildings [Negatives] (Box 89)
  - [East] (Box 89)
  - [Photocopies] (Box 89)
  - Development, University [(Frederic M. Hanes' House)] (Box 89)
  - Dining Halls (West Campus) (Box 89)
  - Divinity School [Construction, Including Architectural Sketch] (Box 89)
  - Doorways and Arches (East Campus) (Box 89)
  - Doorways and Arches (West Campus) (Box 89)
  - Dope Shop [See Union, West Campus] (Box 89)
  - "Doris" Railroad Car of James B. Duke (Box 89)
  - Dormitories, Interiors, East Campus (Box 89)
  - Dormitory, Interior, Trinity College (Box 89)
  - Duke Farm, Hillsborough (Box 89)
  - Duke Forest [See also Forestry School Photos] (Box 89)
  - East Campus Center (Box 89)
  - East Campus Wall (Box 89)
  - East Duke Building (Box 90)
  - East Duke Building [Interior, Including Parlors] (Box 90)
  - East Duke Building [Parlors, Furniture] (Box 90)
  - Edens Quadrangle (Box 90)
  - Edens Quadrangle [Construction] (Box 90)
  - Engineering Building ("Old Red") [Construction] (Box 90)
  - Engineering Building ("Old Red") (Box 90)
  - Engineering, Teer Building [Groundbreaking, Dedication] (Box 90)
  - Entrance Gate, East Campus (Box 90)
  - Entrance Gates, West Campus (Box 90)
  - Entrance Gates, Trinity College, Durham, NC (Box 90)
  - Episcopal Student Center, Central Campus (Box 90)
  - Epworth Inn, East Campus (Box 90)
  - Faculty Housing [Faculty Row, Trinity College, See also Pegram House] (Box 90)
  - Faculty Housing, 1940s [Prefabricated] (Box 90)
  - Fallout Shelters (Box 91)
  - Few Quadrangle (Box 91)
  - Few Quadrangle [Construction] (Box 91)
  - Finch - Yeager Building (DUPAC) (Box 91)
  - Flagpole, Trinity College (Box 91)
  - Flowers Building (Box 91)
  - Flowers Residence [See East Campus Center] (Box 91)
  - Freeman Center for Jewish Life [Proposed] (Box 91)
  - Fuqua School of Business (Box 91)
  - Gardens, pre-1939 [Pre-1939 and Construction] (Box 91)
  - Gardens, 1939 [Dedication] (Box 91)
  - Gardens, 1930s-1940s [General Views] (Box 91)
  - Gardens, 1950s-1970s [General ] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Aerial Views] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Entrances] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Paths, Ponds and Pergola] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [People (posed?)] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Plans] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Snow Scenes] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Statues] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Terraces] (Box 91)
  - Gardens [Color] (Box 91)
  - Gilbert-Addoms Hall, East Campus (Box 92)
  - Giles Hall (Box 92)
  - Golf Course (Box 92)
  - Golf Course [Club House (Old)] (Box 92)
  - Golf Course [Opening] (Box 92)
  - Golf Course [See Map Cabinet Drawer 22] (Box 92)
  - Gothic Bookstore [(Flowers Building)] (Box 92)
  - Graduate Center [Construction] (Box 92)
  - Graduate Center (Box 92)
  - Greenhouse, East Campus (Box 92)
  - Gross Chemistry Building, 1968 [Construction]
    - Exterior (Box 92)
    - Dedication, 1969 (Box 92)
    - Construction (Box 92)
    - Interior (Box 92)
  - Hanes Field (Trinity College, Durham) [See also Athletics - Football, 1920s] (Box 92)
  - Hart (J. Deryl) House (Box 92)
  - Heating Plant, East Campus, 1926 [Construction] (Box 92)
  - Heating Plant, Warehouse, West Campus (Box 92)
  - Highland Hospital, Asheville [Geographic] (Box 92)
  - Hillsborough Quarry [See also Vol. 1 Photos of West Campus Construction] (Box 92)
  - IM Building (Box 93)
  - Infirmary, East Campus (Box 93)
  - Insignia, Duke Seal/Shield (Box 93)
  - Jarvis Hall (Box 93)
  - Jordan Building (Box 93)
  - Kilgo Quadrangle (Box 93)
  - Lamp Posts (Box 93)
  - Law School, 1963 [Dedication] (Box 93)
  - Law School [Original] (Box 93)
  - Law School, 1962- [New Building] (Box 93)
  - Law School, 1963 [Construction] (Box 93)
  - Law School [Log Cabins, Duke Forest, Student Housing] (Box 93)
  - Levine Science Research Center (Box 93)
  - Library [Duplicates for Exhibit] (Box 93)
  - Library, East Campus, Lilly, 2 folders (Box 93)
  - Library, East Campus, Lilly, 1942 [Thomas Room Dedication] (Box 93)
  - Library, East Campus, Lilly [Old Chair to Library] (Box 93)
  - Library, East Campus, Lilly [Exterior] (Box 93)
  - Library (and Chemistry), 1968 [Construction] (Box 93)
  - Library, West Campus, 1948 [Construction] (Box 93)
  - Library, West Campus, 1968 [Construction, Groundbreaking] (Box 93)
  - Library, West Campus, 1968 [Construction] (Box 93)
  - Library, West Campus [Exterior] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, 2003 [Construction] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, pre-1969 [Exterior] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, post-1969 [Perkins Interior] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, 1969 [Dedication] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, 1970 [Interior for Dedication] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, pre-1968 [Includes Flowers Centennial Exhibit] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, post-1969 [Interior] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, pre-1969 [Interior] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus [Rare Book Room] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus, post-1969 [Perkins Interior] (Box 94)
  - Library, West Campus [Mounted Prints Done by a Photography Class] (Box 94)
  - Library, Trinity College, Durham (Box 94)
  - Lowry, Day [Etchings (negatives)] (Box 94)
  - Marine Laboratory [Unmounted Prints] (Box 95)
  - Marine Laboratory [Mounted Prints] (Box 95)
  - Married Student Housing (Box 95)